<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Notes</title><link href="http://znotdead.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://znotdead.github.io/feeds/esl.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://znotdead.github.io/</id><updated>2015-06-21T00:00:00+02:00</updated><entry><title>Special Announcement: Introduction to the United States Course Now Available</title><link href="http://znotdead.github.io/special_announcement_introduction_to_the_united_states_course_now_available-ru.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-06-21T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>znotdead</name></author><id>tag:znotdead.github.io,2015-06-09:special_announcement_introduction_to_the_united_states_course_now_available-ru.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;h3&gt;Special Announcement: Introduction to the United States Course Now Available&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ESLPod.com and the Center for Educational Development present to you Introduction to the United States, a 100 episode course that will teach you about life in the United States, including its government and history.&lt;br /&gt;
This course is based upon the 100 questions used by the U.S. government in its citizenship examination, and includes basic information about the U.S. and its people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each episode of the course begins with a basic question about the U.S., followed by a short answer, and then a detailed explanation of&lt;br /&gt;
that answer.  Each episode is first presented at a slow speed, and then at a normal rate of speech.&lt;br /&gt;
All of the episodes include a special Learning Guide that contains the complete transcript of the episode, as well as vocabulary definitions and sample sentences using the new terms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope you enjoy this special course!&lt;br /&gt;
Introduction to the United States&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="esl"></category></entry><entry><title>Special Announcement: New ESL Podcast Store</title><link href="http://znotdead.github.io/special_announcement_new_esl_podcast_store-ru.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-06-21T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>znotdead</name></author><id>tag:znotdead.github.io,2015-05-26:special_announcement_new_esl_podcast_store-ru.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;h3&gt;Special Announcement: New ESL Podcast Store&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;{'download_href': u'http://media.libsyn.com/media/eslpod/Announcement_Store.mp3', 'text_href': u'show_podcast.php?issue_id=3271449', 'title': u'Special Announcement: New ESL Podcast Store'}&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello, this is Jeff McQuillan from the Center for Educational Development in beautiful Los Angeles, California, with a very special announcement about ESL Podcast.  First, I want to thank all of you for listening and supporting our podcast.  We now have more than 300 podcasts " that's more than 100 hours of free English lessons " available on our website.  Thank you for making that possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now ESL Podcast has even more.  We have just opened the ESL Podcast Store on our website.  This store will sell premium or very special courses on different topics.  Go to our website today at www.eslpod.com to take a look.  We are offering four new premium courses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first is Interview Questions Answered.  This three-hour course is for anyone who wants to learn business English and how to communicate better with American business people.  This course does two things.  It gives you practical suggestions on how to answer business interview questions, and it teaches you the business English you need to answer them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other courses include A Day in the Life of Jeff and A Day in the Life of Lucy.  Many people have asked us to create a complete course that uses all of the common, everyday vocabulary, from getting up in the morning to going to bed at night.  We've created these two ten-part ""Day in the Life" courses that will give you the basic vocabulary used by a man or a woman during the day.  Finally, we have a new English Through Stories mystery, an original, 15-chapter novel called Deadly Letters, by Sarah Gatchitie.  If you love a good story, be sure to listen to Deadly Letters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All four of these special courses come with a complete Learning Guide, with vocabulary, definitions, and a complete transcript of the course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With our new ESL Podcast Store, you can also download individual Learning Guides from our past episodes.  While we hope that all of you will want to try our regular Learning Guide membership, where you get 12 new Learning Guides each month, we know that some of you just want to buy the Learning Guide for some of your favorite podcasts. All of our past Learning Guides are also for sale in the new store.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're very excited about these new courses.  Both Lucy and I are sure that you will enjoy these new premium courses.  As always, if you have suggestions or comments about new courses for ESL Podcast, be sure to email us at eslpod@eslpod.com.  And, of course, you'll want to go to our website today to check out or look at our new store.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Los Angeles, California, I'm Jeff McQuillan.&lt;br /&gt;
Thanks for listening.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="esl"></category></entry><entry><title>Special Announcement: Three New Features</title><link href="http://znotdead.github.io/special_announcement_three_new_features-ru.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-05-20T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>znotdead</name></author><id>tag:znotdead.github.io,2015-05-20:special_announcement_three_new_features-ru.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;h3&gt;Special Announcement:  Three New Features&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;{'download_href': u'http://media.libsyn.com/media/eslpod/Announcement_09_28_07.mp3', 'text_href': u'show_podcast.php?issue_id=4434780', 'title': u'Special Announcement:  Three New Features'}&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Special Announcement:  Three New Features&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello, this is Jeff McQuillan from the Center for Educational Development in beautiful Los Angeles, California, with a special announcement about ESL Podcast. First, I want to thank all of you for listening and supporting our podcast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have three new features we want to tell you about.  First, ESL Podcast now has a blog.  This blog allows us to post messages for our listeners about topics that we don't have time for in our regular podcasts or English Cafes.  It also gives you information that helps you better use our podcasts and also what we might call "insider information" about what is happening at ESL Podcast and with us Jeff and Lucy.  Go to our website today to take a look, at ESLPod.com.  Click on the Blog item in the menu to see our new blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another exciting change is in our ESL Podcast Memberships.  We now have two memberships you can choose from:  a Basic Membership and a Premium Membership.  The Basic Membership gives you 12 new Learning Guides each month, and you have two weeks to download each Learning Guide.&lt;br /&gt;
The Premium Membership gives you access to all of our Learning Guides, over 250!  And, you can download, with our Premium Membership, the Learning Guides anytime, as long as you remain a member.  The Basic Membership is $10 each month; the Premium Membership is $60 for the first month and $10 for each month after that.  So, the first month the Premium  Membership is $60, the second month is $10, and the third month is $10, and so on, until you cancel.  We are very excited to be able to give listeners these two options.  To find out more, go to ESLPod.com and click on "Learning Guides" in the menu for more information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, we have a new course in our ESL Podcast Store.  As many of you already know, we have very special Premium Courses on different topics in the ESL Podcast Store for both business and daily English.  Our new course is called "English for Business Meetings." This course teaches you both formal and informal business English needed to participate in business meetings.  The course follows two meetings from start to finish, and you'll hear different speakers giving information, asking questions, discussing topics, and running the meetings.  The formal business English is appropriate for important meetings, such as for presentations at conferences or annual company meetings. The informal business English used is useful for smaller meetings, such as daily office meetings or for talking with or interacting with your co-workers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're very excited about these new features.  Lucy and I hope that you will visit our website today to check out our new blog, our new memberships, and our new Premium Course, English for Business Meetings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Los Angeles, California, I'm Jeff McQuillan.&lt;br /&gt;
Thanks for listening.&lt;br /&gt;
Special Announcement:  Three New Features&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="esl"></category></entry></feed>